{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"360/15",
			"answer":"360/15",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"420/60",
			"answer":"420/60",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"136/68",
			"answer":"136/68",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"459/27",
			"answer":"459/27",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"747/83",
			"answer":"747/83",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"27.6/4",
			"answer":"27.6/4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.53/0.053",
			"answer":"0.53/0.053",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.244/0.02",
			"answer":"0.244/0.02",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.568/0.008",
			"answer":"0.568/0.008",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"30.8/0.04",
			"answer":"30.8/0.04",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}
	]
}